<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Seth Rollins on bumpXfeed</title>
    <link>https://bumpxfeed.com/tags/seth-rollins/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Seth Rollins on bumpXfeed</description>
    <image>
      <title>bumpXfeed</title>
      <url>https://bumpxfeed.com/images/bf-black.png</url>
      <link>https://bumpxfeed.com/images/bf-black.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bumpxfeed.com/tags/seth-rollins/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>WWE Crown Jewel 2023: A Comprehensive Review of All the Matches</title>
      <link>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/2023-11-04-wwe-crown-jewel-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/2023-11-04-wwe-crown-jewel-2023/</guid>
      <description>WWE Crown Jewel 2023 was a spectacular event that featured some of the best matches of the year. However, not all matches were created equal, and some of them were not worth your time. In this blog post, we will use a metric called the Match Quality Index (MQI) to rank the matches from best to worst, and give you our recommendations on which ones to watch and which ones to skip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Superstars Background Breakdown: WWE Superstars who competed at Backlash 2023 Part 1</title>
      <link>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/superstars-background-breakdown-wwe-superstars-who-competed-at-backlash-2023-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/superstars-background-breakdown-wwe-superstars-who-competed-at-backlash-2023-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Discover the college sports backgrounds of WWE Backlash 2023 superstars! From Bianca Belair&amp;#39;s track and field dominance to Brock Lesnar&amp;#39;s collegiate wrestling championships, these athletes&amp;#39; college experiences shaped their journey to WWE. Part 1 of the Superstars Background Breakdown explores their impressive athletic achievements and showcases the diverse paths that led them to the grand stage of professional wrestling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black x Brave Wrestling Academy: Training with Seth Rollins in Davenport, Iowa</title>
      <link>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/black-x-brave-wrestling-academy-training-with-seth-rollins-in-davenport-iowa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/black-x-brave-wrestling-academy-training-with-seth-rollins-in-davenport-iowa/</guid>
      <description>The Black x Brave Wrestling Academy has been developing talent since 2014. The facility, located in Davenport, Iowa, is equipped with a WWE ring and wide range of gym equipment. Read more about how to train at Seth Rollins&amp;#39; pro wrestling school including the programs they offer and the cost to attend.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
