<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>2024 on bumpXfeed</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2024 on bumpXfeed</description>
    <image>
      <title>bumpXfeed</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/images/bf-black.png</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/images/bf-black.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Flare for the Old, Nostalgic Wrestling Segment with Stunning Steve Austin and Flyin’ Brian Pillman</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/a-flare-for-the-old-nostalgic-wrestling-segment-with-stunning-steve-austin-and-flyin-brian-pillman/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/a-flare-for-the-old-nostalgic-wrestling-segment-with-stunning-steve-austin-and-flyin-brian-pillman/</guid>
      <description>In this entertaining segment, the legendary “Nature Boy” Ric Flair is played by Flyin&amp;#39; Brian Pillman and hosts a celebration of nostalgia called “A Flare for the Old.” The event features the seven, eight, or nine-time world champion (the count seems a bit fuzzy!) and his maid, Pate. The crowd erupts as Stunning Steve Austin, one half of the World Tag Team Champions, takes the stage. Amid applause and boos, Steve shares insights about the Hollywood Blondes’ tag team success. But the real drama unfolds when Arn Anderson enters the ring, leading to an unexpected showdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tama Tonga: From the Indies to WWE SmackDown</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/tama-tonga-from-the-indies-to-wwe-smackdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/tama-tonga-from-the-indies-to-wwe-smackdown/</guid>
      <description>Alipate Aloisio Leone, better known by his ring name Tama Tonga, has left an indelible mark on the world of professional wrestling. From his early days on the independent circuit to his recent debut in WWE, let&amp;#39;s explore the fascinating journey of this Tongan powerhouse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-Pandemic Prospects: WWE Performance Center&#39;s December 2020 Trainee Class</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/pre-pandemic-prospects-wwe-performance-centers-december-2020-trainee-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/pre-pandemic-prospects-wwe-performance-centers-december-2020-trainee-class/</guid>
      <description>A bumpxfeed exclusive: We&amp;#39;ll take a look at the December 2020 WWE Performance Center trainees&amp;#39; professional wrestling careers from training at the PC to where they are now in 2024.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
