<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Florida on bumpXfeed</title>
    <link>https://bumpxfeed.com/tags/florida/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Florida on bumpXfeed</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 12:22:49 +1100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://bumpxfeed.com/tags/florida/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2015 WWE Performance Center Trainees; Where Are They Now?</title>
      <link>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/2015-wwe-performance-center-trainees-where-are-they-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/2015-wwe-performance-center-trainees-where-are-they-now/</guid>
      <description>The WWE was actively recruiting, globally, for the April 2015 Performance Center class. Some made it to the main WWE roster and are still active, some achieved main roster superstardom and succeeded outside of WWE, while others didn&amp;rsquo;t make it beyond NXT. Let&amp;rsquo;s break down the WWE Performance Center class of 2015 and see what they are up to today (2023).&#xA;🇦🇺 Australia Cassie McIntosh aka Peyton Royce aka Cassie Lee (Born in Sydney, resided in Melbourne, Australia) Cassie McIntosh got her pro wrestling training with Pro Wrestling Australia in 2009 and also trained with Lance Storm at his now defunct academy, in 2012.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Guide to Trying Out for WWE&#39;s Performance Center / Tips to Become a WWE Sports Entertainer</title>
      <link>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/2023-04-01-the-ultimate-guide-to-trying-out-for-wwes-performance-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/2023-04-01-the-ultimate-guide-to-trying-out-for-wwes-performance-center/</guid>
      <description>Step 1 Apply and submit your application to be a WWE Sports Entertainer/Pro Wrestler As of Friday, December 30, 2022, WWE&amp;rsquo;s Recruit website is live and accepting applications. Click the &amp;ldquo;APPLY NOW&amp;rdquo; link as seen in the screenshot, or scroll down to get started! The pop-up/modal asks for your date of birth and if you are a college athlete or not.&#xA;If you are a college athlete, you will be taken to an NIL questionnaire If you are NOT a college athlete, you will be taken to the general questionnaire Step 2 Accept an invitation from WWE After submitting your application, WWE may contact you within 4-6 weeks notice to attend a tryout.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
