<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on bump x feed</title>
    <link>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on bump x feed</description>
    <image>
      <title>bump x feed</title>
      <url>https://bumpxfeed.com/images/bf-black.png</url>
      <link>https://bumpxfeed.com/images/bf-black.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 20:53:43 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Train with Seth &#34;Freakin&#34; Rollins and his group at the Black x Brave Wrestling Academy in Davenport, Iowa</title>
      <link>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/train-with-seth-freakin-rollins-and-his-group-at-the-black-x-brave-wrestling-academy-in-davenport-iowa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 20:53:43 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/train-with-seth-freakin-rollins-and-his-group-at-the-black-x-brave-wrestling-academy-in-davenport-iowa/</guid>
      <description>Information about Seth Rollins&amp;#39; pro wrestling school, Black x Brave Wrestling Academy, located in Davenport, Iowa. Learn more about their programs and the cost to attend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn the Art of Pro Wrestling at the World-Famous Monster Factory in Paulsboro, New Jersey</title>
      <link>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/learn-the-art-of-pro-wrestling-at-the-world-famous-monster-factory-in-paulsboro-new-jersey/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/learn-the-art-of-pro-wrestling-at-the-world-famous-monster-factory-in-paulsboro-new-jersey/</guid>
      <description>Information about the World Famous Monster Factory training center located in Paulsboro, New Jersey. Learn more about their programs and the cost to attend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Guide to Trying Out for WWE&#39;s Performance Center / Tips to Become a WWE Sports Entertainer</title>
      <link>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/the-ultimate-guide-to-trying-out-for-wwes-performance-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 16:32:30 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/the-ultimate-guide-to-trying-out-for-wwes-performance-center/</guid>
      <description>So you want to be a pro wrestler / sports entertainer for the biggest wrestling company in the world? They actually made it easy for you to join and train at the world famous &amp;ldquo;PC&amp;rdquo;, aka the WWE Performance Center, located in Orlando, Florida. WWE (World Wrestling Entertainment) is constantly looking for fresh talent and even created a website to make the process easier. Scroll down to learn more!
Step 1 Apply and submit your application to be a WWE Sports Entertainer/Pro Wrestler As of Friday, December 30, 2022, WWE&amp;rsquo;s Recruit website is live and accepting applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pro Wrestling Training to Main Roster: Austin Theory from the WWE</title>
      <link>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/pro-wrestling-training-to-main-roster-austin-theory-from-the-wwe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/pro-wrestling-training-to-main-roster-austin-theory-from-the-wwe/</guid>
      <description>Austin Theory defeated his childhood hero, WWE legend John Cena, by pinfall at Wrestlemania 39 in Los Angeles, California. While some may argue that his success has been quick, he&amp;rsquo;s actually been wrestling matches since 2016. The 25 year old has 7 years of experience in the wrestling business, not including his training.
Athletic Background Austin Theory was involved with bodybuilding before he started training as a Professional Wrestler.
2016 Austin Theory makes his Pro Wrestling Debut He began his wrestling career at a young age and trained at the World Wrestling Alliance 4 (WWA4) wrestling school in Atlanta, Georgia.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
