<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>bumpXfeed</title>
    <link>https://bumpxfeed.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on bumpXfeed</description>
    <image>
      <title>bumpXfeed</title>
      <url>https://bumpxfeed.com/images/bf-black.png</url>
      <link>https://bumpxfeed.com/images/bf-black.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 22:17:34 +1100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://bumpxfeed.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>WWE Survivor Series 2023: WarGames Steal the Show, Orton &amp; Punk Return, Fans React!</title>
      <link>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/2023/wwe-survivor-series-2023-wargames-steal-the-show-orton--punk-return-fans-react/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/2023/wwe-survivor-series-2023-wargames-steal-the-show-orton--punk-return-fans-react/</guid>
      <description>WWE Survivor Series 2023 delivered a thrilling night of action with two brutal WarGames matches, the shocking return of Randy Orton and CM Punk, and a solid overall performance. A closer look at the fan reactions reveals key insights into the highlights and potential areas for improvement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WWE Royal Rumble 2023: The Good, The Bad, and The Ugly</title>
      <link>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/2023/wwe-royal-rumble-2023-the-good-the-bad-and-the-ugly/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/2023/wwe-royal-rumble-2023-the-good-the-bad-and-the-ugly/</guid>
      <description>The WWE Royal Rumble 2023 was a night of surprises, shocks, and shenanigans. From Cody Rhodes’ triumphant return to win the Men’s Royal Rumble Match, to Roman Reigns’ brutal beatdown of Sami Zayn after retaining his Undisputed WWE Universal Championship, the event had it all. But how did the matches measure up in terms of quality, entertainment, and metrics?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WWE Backlash 2023: The Best and Worst Matches to Watch</title>
      <link>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/2023/wwe-backlash-2023-the-best-and-worst-matches-to-watch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/2023/wwe-backlash-2023-the-best-and-worst-matches-to-watch/</guid>
      <description>A blog post that ranks the matches from WWE Backlash 2023 based on a metric called the Match Quality Index (MQI), which combines the match rating &amp;amp; match length provided by Cageematch, and the WON rating, and gives recommendations on which ones to watch and which ones to skip.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequently Asked Questions about the Match Quality Index (MQI)</title>
      <link>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/2023/frequently-asked-questions-about-the-match-quality-index-mqi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/2023/frequently-asked-questions-about-the-match-quality-index-mqi/</guid>
      <description>A FAQ page that explains what the Match Quality Index (MQI) is and how it works, and how it can help you decide which matches to watch and which ones to skip from WWE, AEW, TNA/Impact, ROH, and other pro wrestling events.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WWE Crown Jewel 2023: A Comprehensive Review of All the Matches</title>
      <link>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/2023/wwe-crown-jewel-2023-a-comprehensive-review-of-all-the-matches/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/2023/wwe-crown-jewel-2023-a-comprehensive-review-of-all-the-matches/</guid>
      <description>WWE Crown Jewel 2023 was a spectacular event that featured some of the best matches of the year. However, not all matches were created equal, and some of them were not worth your time. In this blog post, we will use a metric called the Match Quality Index (MQI) to rank the matches from best to worst, and give you our recommendations on which ones to watch and which ones to skip.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to choose the right pro wrestling school for you</title>
      <link>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/2023/how-to-choose-the-right-pro-wrestling-school-for-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/2023/how-to-choose-the-right-pro-wrestling-school-for-you/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;#39;re serious about becoming a professional wrestler, then choosing the right school is essential. A good school will teach you the fundamentals of the sport, help you develop your skills, and prepare you for the rigors of the wrestling business. But with so many different schools out there, it can be tough to know where to start. That&amp;#39;s why we&amp;#39;ve put together this guide to help you choose the right pro wrestling school for you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superstars Background Breakdown: WWE Superstars who competed at Backlash 2023 Part 1</title>
      <link>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/2023/superstars-background-breakdown-wwe-superstars-who-competed-at-backlash-2023-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/2023/superstars-background-breakdown-wwe-superstars-who-competed-at-backlash-2023-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Discover the college sports backgrounds of WWE Backlash 2023 superstars! From Bianca Belair&amp;#39;s track and field dominance to Brock Lesnar&amp;#39;s collegiate wrestling championships, these athletes&amp;#39; college experiences shaped their journey to WWE. Part 1 of the Superstars Background Breakdown explores their impressive athletic achievements and showcases the diverse paths that led them to the grand stage of professional wrestling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://bumpxfeed.com/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bumpxfeed.com/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy policy for bumpxfeed.com. Last updated May 2, 2023</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2015 WWE Performance Center Trainees; Where Are They Now?</title>
      <link>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/2023/2015-wwe-performance-center-trainees-where-are-they-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/2023/2015-wwe-performance-center-trainees-where-are-they-now/</guid>
      <description>A bumpxfeed exclusive: We&amp;#39;ll take a look at the 2015 WWE Performance Center trainees&amp;#39; professional wrestling careers from training to where they are now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Take Your Wrestling Career to the Next Level at the NYWC Training Academy</title>
      <link>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/2023/take-your-wrestling-career-to-the-next-level-at-the-nywc-training-academy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/2023/take-your-wrestling-career-to-the-next-level-at-the-nywc-training-academy/</guid>
      <description>Are you dreaming of becoming a successful professional wrestler? Do you want to learn from experienced trainers who have worked with WWE, ROH, and other top promotions? Look no further than NYWC Training Academy, Long Island&amp;#39;s oldest and most successful wrestling school. With a proven track record of producing dynamic wrestlers who have gone on to work with WWE, AEW, Impact, and NJPW, NYWC offers comprehensive training led by top trainers Mike Mondo and Michael Mistretta. From the basics to advanced techniques, you&amp;#39;ll learn everything you need to know to be successful in the industry. Join the ranks of NYWC graduates like Zack Ryder/Matt Cardona, Curt Hawkins/Brian Myers, Tony Nese, and more. Training is affordable at just $200 per month, with flexible scheduling options available. Don&amp;#39;t wait to take your wrestling career to the next level – enroll in NYWC Training Academy today!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro Wrestling Training to Main Roster: Austin Theory from the WWE</title>
      <link>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/2023/pro-wrestling-training-to-main-roster-austin-theory-from-the-wwe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/2023/pro-wrestling-training-to-main-roster-austin-theory-from-the-wwe/</guid>
      <description>Austin Theory defeated his childhood hero, WWE legend John Cena, by pinfall at Wrestlemania 39 in Los Angeles, California. While some may argue that his success has been quick, he&amp;#39;s actually been wrestling matches since 2016. The 25 year old has 7 years of experience in the wrestling business, not including his training.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black x Brave Wrestling Academy: Training with Seth Rollins in Davenport, Iowa</title>
      <link>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/2023/black-x-brave-wrestling-academy-training-with-seth-rollins-in-davenport-iowa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/2023/black-x-brave-wrestling-academy-training-with-seth-rollins-in-davenport-iowa/</guid>
      <description>The Black x Brave Wrestling Academy has been developing talent since 2014. The facility, located in Davenport, Iowa, is equipped with a WWE ring and wide range of gym equipment. Read more about how to train at Seth Rollins&amp;#39; pro wrestling school including the programs they offer and the cost to attend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The World Famous Monster Factory: Developing Pro Wrestling Talent Since 1983</title>
      <link>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/2023/the-world-famous-monster-factory-developing-pro-wrestling-talent-since-1983/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/2023/the-world-famous-monster-factory-developing-pro-wrestling-talent-since-1983/</guid>
      <description>The World Famous Monster Factory, located in Paulsboro, New Jersey, has been developing wrestling talent since 1983. The school was founded by &amp;#34;Pretty Boy&amp;#34; Larry Sharpe and &amp;#34;Nature Boy&amp;#34; Buddy Rogers, and in 2011, Danny Cage bought and rebranded the training center. Cage coaches, owns, and operates the school, continuing the tradition of developing some of the best wrestlers in the industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://bumpxfeed.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bumpxfeed.com/about/</guid>
      <description>About the author of bump x feed, Jalen Wu</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Guide to Trying Out for WWE&#39;s Performance Center</title>
      <link>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/2023/the-ultimate-guide-to-try-out-for-wwe-performance-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bumpxfeed.com/posts/2023/the-ultimate-guide-to-try-out-for-wwe-performance-center/</guid>
      <description>So you want to be a pro wrestler / sports entertainer for the biggest wrestling company in the world? They actually made it easy for you to join and train at the world famous PC, aka the WWE Performance Center, located in Orlando, Florida. WWE (World Wrestling Entertainment) is constantly looking for fresh talent and even created a website to make the process easier. Scroll down to learn more!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
