<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WWE on bumpXfeed</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/wwe/</link>
    <description>Recent content in WWE on bumpXfeed</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 23:21:58 +1100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/wwe/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>WWE Survivor Series 2023: WarGames Steal the Show, Orton &amp; Punk Return, Fans React!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023-11-25-wwe-survivor-series-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023-11-25-wwe-survivor-series-2023/</guid>
      <description>WWE Survivor Series 2023: WarGames Steal the Show, Orton &amp;amp; Punk Return, Fans React! WWE Survivor Series 2023 delivered a thrilling night of action with two brutal WarGames matches, the shocking return of Randy Orton and CM Punk, and a solid overall performance. A closer look at the fan reactions reveals key insights into the highlights and potential areas for improvement.&#xA;WarGames Dominate: The event kicked off with the highly anticipated Women&amp;rsquo;s WarGames match, which received praise for its storytelling and high-impact spots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WWE Vengeance Day 2023: The Good, The Bad, and The MQI</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023-02-04-wwe-nxt-vengeance-day-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023-02-04-wwe-nxt-vengeance-day-2023/</guid>
      <description>The Good WWE NXT North American Title Match: Wes Lee (c) vs. Dijak MQI Score: 8.464&#xA;This was the match of the night, hands down. Wes Lee and Dijak put on a clinic of athleticism, power, and agility. The two men traded high-flying moves, hard-hitting strikes, and near-falls that kept the fans on the edge of their seats. Lee retained his title after hitting a 450 splash from the top rope, but Dijak earned his respect and the crowd&amp;rsquo;s admiration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WWE Vengeance Day 2023: The Good, The Bad, and The MQI</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/wwe-vengeance-day-2023-the-good-the-bad-and-the-mqi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/wwe-vengeance-day-2023-the-good-the-bad-and-the-mqi/</guid>
      <description>The Good WWE NXT North American Title Match: Wes Lee (c) vs. Dijak MQI Score: 8.464&#xA;This was the match of the night, hands down. Wes Lee and Dijak put on a clinic of athleticism, power, and agility. The two men traded high-flying moves, hard-hitting strikes, and near-falls that kept the fans on the edge of their seats. Lee retained his title after hitting a 450 splash from the top rope, but Dijak earned his respect and the crowd&amp;rsquo;s admiration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WWE Royal Rumble 2023: The Good, The Bad, and The Ugly</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023-01-28-wwe-royal-rumble-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023-01-28-wwe-royal-rumble-2023/</guid>
      <description>Yes, you read that right. Metrics. We&amp;rsquo;re not talking about the usual counting of pins, submissions, or eliminations. We&amp;rsquo;re talking about the Match Quality Index (MQI), a data-driven metric that evaluates the quality of professional wrestling matches. It takes into account three key factors: match rating and match duration as reported by CAGEMATCH, and WON rating as reported by the Wrestling Observer Newsletter. The MQI is calculated using the following formula:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WWE Backlash 2023: The Best and Worst Matches to Watch</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023-05-06-wwe-backlash-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023-05-06-wwe-backlash-2023/</guid>
      <description>In the world of professional wrestling, where athleticism, storytelling, and raw emotion intertwine, determining the true quality of a match can be a subjective endeavor. However, with the introduction of the Match Quality Index (MQI), a data-driven approach has emerged to shed light on the intricate factors that contribute to an exceptional wrestling bout.&#xA;The MQI takes into account three key metrics: match rating, match duration, and WON rating. Match rating reflects the overall sentiment of fans, while match duration highlights the intensity and endurance displayed by the wrestlers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequently Asked Questions about the Match Quality Index (MQI)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023-11-10-faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023-11-10-faq/</guid>
      <description>Frequently Asked Questions about the Match Quality Index (MQI)&#xA;What is the MQI? The Match Quality Index (MQI) is a data-driven metric that evaluates the quality of professional wrestling matches. It takes into account three key factors: match rating and match duration as reported by CAGEMATCH, and WON rating.&#xA;The WON rating is a subjective measure of the quality of the match, based on the ratings from the Wrestling Observer Newsletter, a newsletter that covers professional wrestling and mixed martial arts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequently Asked Questions about the Match Quality Index (MQI)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/frequently-asked-questions-about-the-match-quality-index-mqi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/frequently-asked-questions-about-the-match-quality-index-mqi/</guid>
      <description>Frequently Asked Questions about the Match Quality Index (MQI)&#xA;What is the MQI? The Match Quality Index (MQI) is a data-driven metric that evaluates the quality of professional wrestling matches. It takes into account three key factors: match rating and match duration as reported by CAGEMATCH, and WON rating.&#xA;The WON rating is a subjective measure of the quality of the match, based on the ratings from the Wrestling Observer Newsletter, a newsletter that covers professional wrestling and mixed martial arts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WWE Crown Jewel 2023: A Comprehensive Review of All the Matches</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023-11-04-wwe-crown-jewel-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023-11-04-wwe-crown-jewel-2023/</guid>
      <description>WWE Crown Jewel 2023 was a historic event that featured some of the best and worst matches of the year, as well as some controversial outcomes. Here are the match ratings, highlights and analysis of all the matches of the event, based on the Match Quality Index (MQI), which combines the match duration, the fan rating and the Wrestling Observer Newsletter (WON) rating.&#xA;Best Match: Seth Rollins vs. Drew McIntyre - MQI: 8.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WWE Crown Jewel 2023: A Comprehensive Review of All the Matches</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/wwe-crown-jewel-2023-a-comprehensive-review-of-all-the-matches/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/wwe-crown-jewel-2023-a-comprehensive-review-of-all-the-matches/</guid>
      <description>WWE Crown Jewel 2023 was a historic event that featured some of the best and worst matches of the year, as well as some controversial outcomes. Here are the match ratings, highlights and analysis of all the matches of the event, based on the Match Quality Index (MQI), which combines the match duration, the fan rating and the Wrestling Observer Newsletter (WON) rating.&#xA;Best Match: Seth Rollins vs. Drew McIntyre - MQI: 8.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superstars Background Breakdown: WWE Superstars who competed at Backlash 2023 Part 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023-06-30-superstars-background-breakdown-wwe-superstars-who-competed-at-backlash-2023-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023-06-30-superstars-background-breakdown-wwe-superstars-who-competed-at-backlash-2023-part-2/</guid>
      <description>In part 1 of Superstars Background Breakdown: WWE Superstars who competed at Backlash 2023, we took a look at the WWE superstars who had collegiate athletic backgrounds before joining World Wrestling Entertainment. In part 2, we&amp;rsquo;ll showcase the superstars who started their careers on the independents before becoming superstars in the WWE.&#xA;There were a total of 19 professional wrestlers that performed on the WWE premium live event that had different backgrounds before joining the main roster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superstars Background Breakdown: WWE Superstars who competed at Backlash 2023 Part 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023-05-26-superstars-background-breakdown-wwe-superstars-who-competed-at-backlash-2023-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023-05-26-superstars-background-breakdown-wwe-superstars-who-competed-at-backlash-2023-part-1/</guid>
      <description>The 2023 Backlash, held in Puerto Rico, was an action-packed WWE event featuring Bad Bunny in a thrilling San Juan Street Fight. Cody Rhodes emerged victorious in the final match, while other standout moments included The Bloodline&amp;rsquo;s triumph and Bianca Belair&amp;rsquo;s record-breaking title defense. Fans and critics alike praised the event, highlighting the memorable San Juan Street Fight and the Raw Women&amp;rsquo;s Championship match. #WWE #Backlash2023&#xA;WWE Backlash 2023 Results</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2015 WWE Performance Center Trainees; Where Are They Now?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2015-wwe-performance-center-trainees-where-are-they-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2015-wwe-performance-center-trainees-where-are-they-now/</guid>
      <description>The WWE was actively recruiting, globally, for the April 2015 Performance Center class. Some made it to the main WWE roster and are still active, some achieved main roster superstardom and succeeded outside of WWE, while others didn&amp;rsquo;t make it beyond NXT. Let&amp;rsquo;s break down the WWE Performance Center class of 2015 and see what they are up to today (2023).&#xA;🇦🇺 Australia Cassie McIntosh aka Peyton Royce aka Cassie Lee (Born in Sydney, resided in Melbourne, Australia) Cassie McIntosh got her pro wrestling training with Pro Wrestling Australia in 2009 and also trained with Lance Storm at his now defunct academy, in 2012.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro Wrestling Training to Main Roster: Austin Theory from the WWE</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023-04-10-pro-wrestling-training-to-main-roster-austin-theory-from-the-wwe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023-04-10-pro-wrestling-training-to-main-roster-austin-theory-from-the-wwe/</guid>
      <description>Attention wrestling fans! If you&amp;rsquo;re a fan of professional wrestling, then you&amp;rsquo;ve probably heard of Austin Theory. He&amp;rsquo;s one of the newest and most promising faces in the industry. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll take a look at his athletic background, his journey to becoming a WWE superstar, and his rise to becoming the United States Champion.&#xA;Austin Theory&amp;rsquo;s Athletic Background Before Austin Theory became a professional wrestler, he was involved in bodybuilding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Guide to Trying Out for WWE&#39;s Performance Center / Tips to Become a WWE Sports Entertainer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023-04-01-the-ultimate-guide-to-trying-out-for-wwes-performance-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023-04-01-the-ultimate-guide-to-trying-out-for-wwes-performance-center/</guid>
      <description>Step 1 Apply and submit your application to be a WWE Sports Entertainer/Pro Wrestler As of Friday, December 30, 2022, WWE&amp;rsquo;s Recruit website is live and accepting applications. Click the &amp;ldquo;APPLY NOW&amp;rdquo; link as seen in the screenshot, or scroll down to get started! The pop-up/modal asks for your date of birth and if you are a college athlete or not.&#xA;If you are a college athlete, you will be taken to an NIL questionnaire If you are NOT a college athlete, you will be taken to the general questionnaire Step 2 Accept an invitation from WWE After submitting your application, WWE may contact you within 4-6 weeks notice to attend a tryout.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
